http://www.gauley.com/about-us/policies/terms-and-conditions/

800-759-7238CONTACT
Why usABOUTBrochurePoliciesStaffCHOOSE A TRIPRAFTINGWhich Trip Is Right For Me?Upper New Kids (Kids / Family)Lower New (Adventure)Lower Gauley (Adventure)Upper Gauley (Thrill Plus )Deals & SpecialsMulti-Day TripsRapid Classificationsstart yourADVENTURESWhitewater RaftingHorseback RidingFishingMountain BikingMore OutdoorsReady for funPLANDiningGorge Trip BlogWhat to KnowNearby AttractionsFind a bedSTAYCabinsCampingMeadow River CampgroundGET IN TOUCHCONTACTEmploymentDirectionsReleases
Terms and Conditions
Privacy PolicyThanks for visiting www.gauley.com . Our goal is to protect your privacy, below you will find how we use personal information collected by www.gauley.com Please read privacy policy before providing any personal information or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for www.gauley.com site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.Collection Of InformationWe collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, phone numbers etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request for rafting, lodging, and other related adventures. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists, special updates, or to make reservations via credit or debit cards.Distribution Of InformationWe may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data SecurityYour personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.Privacy Contact InformationIf you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:e-mail: adventure@gauley.comPhone: 304-574-3008We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Best trip ever with Bryan as our guide. We will return for more adventures!! Loved the video too, great souvenir of our trip! Thanks!
– Sharon H.
Book NowNEW & GAULEY
DirectionsGET ACTIVEADVENTURESRAFTING PACKAGESPLACES TO STAYPLAN YOUR TRIPNEWSLETTER
Stay INFORMED with the latest news & events
800-759-7238
© 2020 New and Gauley , West VirginiaPrivacy Policy
MenuABOUT USBrochurePoliciesTerms and ConditionsStaffADVENTURESFishingHorseback RidingMore OutdoorsMountain BikingWhitewater RaftingCONTACTDirectionsEmploymentGeneral InquiryHomeHomepageInner Template TestPLAN YOUR TRIPDiningGorge Trip BlogLodgingNearby AttractionsWhat to KnowRAFTINGDeals & SpecialsMulti-Day TripsWhich Trip Is Right For Me?Lower Gauley (Thrill)Lower New (Family)Upper Gauley (Extreme)Upper NewRAFTING PACKAGESRapid ClassificationsReleasesRequest a GuideSample PageSTAYCabinsCampingMeadow River CampgroundThank You
Top
